Prove your innocence to an AI judge or face execution.
Mercy is a science fiction, action, thriller film directed by Timur Bekmambetov.
In the near future, a detective stands on trial accused of murdering his wife.
He has ninety minutes to prove his innocence to the advanced AI Judge
he once championed, before it determines his fate.
Chris Raven, played by Chris Pratt.
Judge Maddox, played by Rebecca Ferguson.
Jacqueline 'Jaq' Diallo, played by Kali Reis.
Nicole Raven (née Martin), played by Annabelle Wallis.
Robert 'Rob' Nelson, played by Chris Sullivan.
Britt Raven, played by Kylie Rogers.
Mercy is a 2026 American science fiction action thriller film directed by Timur Bekmambetov,
written by Marco van Belle, and produced by Charles Roven and Bekmambetov.
The film stars Chris Pratt, Rebecca Ferguson, Kali Reis,
Annabelle Wallis, Chris Sullivan, and Kylie Rogers.
Mercy was released in the United States by Amazon
MGM Studios on January 23, 2026.
The film received negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of race against time, artificial intelligence (a.i.),
los angeles, california, false accusations, innocent suspect.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.